That was the 10th time
I've peed here.
여기 와서 오줌
열 번이나 눴다
It's also the 10th time
you've told us.
그 얘기 들은 것도 열 번째다
Sorry, it must be hard to hear.
듣기 피곤했다면 미안하다
It's easier having babies playing
"Bring in Da Funk" on your bladder!
방광을 짓누르는 세쌍둥이
넣고 다니는 건 일도 아냐
I am so sick of being pregnant. God!
이거 진짜 못할 짓이다
등을 바닥에 대고 자야 되는데
등이 아파 잠을 잘 수가 있나
I can't sleep, except on my back,
which hurt. So I can't sleep.
커피 한 잔이 유일한 행복인데
카페인도 안돼, 왜? 임산부니까
My only happiness
is from a cup of coffee...
...which is decaf
because I'm pregnant!
You want a cookie?
피비, 과자 먹을래?
Thank you so much!
정말 고맙다
So, honey, how are those
mood swings coming?
근데 피비?
임신우울증은 어때?
I haven't had any yet.
아직 안 왔어
The One with the
Worst Best Man Ever
Hey, guys.
- 얘들아
- 어서 와
All right, here's the ring.
봐
이게 결혼반지야
Yes, yes!
A thousand times, yes!
네, 좋아요
승낙할게요
Any ideas for the bachelor party?
총각파티는 어떻게 됐어?
Before rings and bachelor parties, you have
to decide who your best man will be.
결혼반지나 총각파티보다
신랑들러리부터 결정해야지
Oh, it's awkward.
이거 껄끄러운데, 껄끄러워
I already asked Chandler.
벌써 챈들러한테 부탁했어
He got to do it
at your first wedding.
뭐? 너 처음 결혼할 때도
얘가 했잖아
그 정도는 네가 이해해줘야지
너보다 더 오랜 친구사이잖아
I figured you'd understand.
I've known him longer.
I don't have any brothers.
I'll never be a best man.
야, 난 형제도 없어서
평생 기회가 없을 거야
나 결혼할 때 하면 되지
You can be the best man
when I get married.
I'll never get to be a best man!
그럼 죽었다 깨도 못하겠네
Wait, wait.
잠깐, 난 두 번이나 써줬는데
넌 날 들러리로 안 세운다고?
So you'll be my best man twice,
and I won't be yours at all?
Of course, you can be my best man.
뭐, 물론 너도 할 수 있지
그럼 난? 나 시켜준댔잖아
-What about me? You said I could.
-I'm not getting married!
내가 지금 장가 간데?
It's a question
for science-fiction writers.
아주 공상과학소설을 써라
I can't believe it's not me.
이렇게 배신 때려도 되냐?
야, 당연히 날 찍어야지
-How could it not be me?
-I'm not even
난 아직... 전혀...
You know what?
That's it.
그럼 좋아, 나도 마음 정했어
조이, 신랑들러리는 이제 너야
From now on,
Joey will be my best man.
고렇지! 미안해서 어쩌냐
Shame about you, though.
관두지 못해?
-Stop it.
-What?
왜
One of the babies is kicking.
애가 발길질을 하잖아
That's a good thing.
그건 좋은 현상 아냐?
It's not kicking me.
It's kicking another baby.
옆에 있는 다른 애를 찬다니까
성질 돋구면 가서 혼내준다
Don't make me come in there!
- 얘들아
- 어서 와
Do you have a big bowl
I can borrow?
큰 그릇 하나만 빌릴까?
There's one under the cabinet.
그 밑에 하나 있어
- 고마워
- 어디다 쓰게?
-Why do you need it?
-We're having a party tomorrow night.
내일 큰 파티가 있거든
또 보자
얘, 잠깐만
우린 초대 안 해?
-Are you planning on inviting us?
-No. Later!
아서라, 또 보자
당장 들어오지 못해
트리비아니!
Get your ass back here, Tribbiani!
Hormones.
호르몬 과다야
How come you're having a party
and we're not invited?
피비 얘기는 어떻게 우리를
빼놓고 파티를 하냐는 거지
-It's Ross' bachelor party.
-So?
로스의 총각파티거든
그래서?
Are you bachelors?
너희 총각이냐?
아니
그럼 스트리퍼야?
Are you strippers?
아니
Then you're not invited.
그니까 빠져줘
Then you're not invited
to our party either.
좋아, 우리 파티에도
너희들 초대 안 할래
What party?
무슨 파티인데?
그게, 음...
Phoebe's baby shower.
예비엄마를 위한 파티
Baby shower? That so doesn't sound
like something I want to do.
예비엄마? 그런 거 진짜
하고 싶지 않다, 또 보자
I can't believe
I'm going to have a party.
그럼 날 위한 파티잖아
That's so great.
A party!
너무 신난다
파티라니, 예!
내가 왜 이러니
I don't know why.
This is what I got going
for the party liquor-wise.
술은 이렇게 준비하는 거야
-Get a lot of liquor.
-Great.
- 엄청 많이
- 좋다, 그래
In terms of the invite list,
I got you, me and Chandler.
그리고 초대할 사람은
너하고 나, 챈들러
우리 얘기 들었을 테니까
건터도 안 부를 순 없고
I'll invite Gunther because
we're talking pretty loud.
I'll be there.
갈게
명심해라, 아무리 네 파티지만
박물관 괴짜들은 조금만 불러
I know it's your party...
...but I'd like to limit
the number of museum geeks.
좋아, 인류학자는 빼고
공룡학자들만 초대하자
Let's not invite any anthropologists.
Just the dinosaur dudes.
We'll need a six-pack of Zima.
그럼 저알코올음료
여섯 상자 추가
Hey, what are you doing?
얘들아, 뭐하니?
그냥 내 신랑들러리랑
총각파티 계획 짜는데
Just planning my bachelor party
with my best man.
지난번보다 잘되길 빈다
Good luck trying
to top the last one.
It won't be that difficult
since this one won't be...
이번엔 피자헛 지하도 아닌데
그게 뭐 어렵겠어?
...in the basement of a Pizza Hut.
I'm Ross, I'm Ross.
I'm too good for the Hut.
잘난 로스 선생한테
피자헛이 웬 말이오
I gotta go pick up Ben.
Everything sounds great.
벤 데리러 가야 돼
지금까지는 다 좋아
그냥 차분하게 나가자
가볍게 포커나 하든지
Keep it on the mellow side.
A few guys hanging out.
-No strippers or anything.
-You got it.
스트리퍼는 안돼, 알았지?
- 수신양호
- 그래, 이따 보자
See you later.
Have fun planning your mellow party.
차분한 총각파티 잘해보셔
There will be strippers. He didn't
say anything about no strippers.
스트리퍼도 올 거야, 로스는
스트리퍼 얘기 안 했으니까
He just said, "No strippers."
방금 안 된다고 했잖아
I chose not to hear that.
오, 못 들은 걸로 할래
Look what I got, look what I got!
내가 뭐 샀나 볼래?
이런 것도 아동용이 있더라
They make these for little people!
시골아동용?
Little Village People.
그럼 이걸 한번 봐
내 맘에 쏙 들어
Look at this one.
This is my favorite.
와, 너무 예쁘다
That is so sweet.
Phoebe will love dressing them.
피비가 입히면서
얼마나 좋아할까
하지만 옷 입힐 사람은
피비가 아니잖아
Except she won't be the one
who gets to dress them.
She won't get to keep the babies.
피비가 키우는 게 아니었지?
My God, we are throwing
the most depressing baby shower!
망할! 이러다 엄청 우울한
예비엄마파티 되겠다
잠깐, 피비가 출산 후에
쓸 수 있는 선물은 어때
Unless we give her all gifts
she can use after her pregnancy.
Like regular coffee. Tequila!
레귤러커피나 테킬라
담배도 좋고
-A carton of cigarettes!
-She doesn't smoke.
담배 안 피우는데?
말이 그렇다고
-It's the thought that counts.
-It's a great idea.
멋진 생각이야, 피비가 늘 갖고
싶어하던 가죽바지도 있잖아
And those leather pants
she's always wanted!
너무 좋아할 거야
She'll love that!
What the hell is this?
이게 대체 뭐야?
두 달 간 쓰지도 못할 걸 받고
내가 기뻐할 거라고 생각했니?
You thought it'd make me feel better?
To give me something
I can't use for two months?
This sucks!
환장하겠다
-Who gave me this?
-Well, l
누가 사온 거야
쟤들이 네가
좋아할 거래서...
They told me you like them.
알았다, 내가 못됐구나
생애 최고의 선물인데
All right, then I'm wrong. It's a great gift.
The best present I ever got!
What's my next present?
좋아, 다음 선물 내놔봐
We don't have anything.
이제 없는데
All right, fine, then this is over.
그럼 끝내자
젠장!
Balloons!
터져라!
-Listen, about the stripper....
-Yeah?
저 스트리퍼 말인데
- 그래...
- 잘 불렀다!
Good call!
So I'll be hosting
your next bachelor party?
다음 총각파티 때도
날 선택해야겠지?
Joey, I'm kind of hoping
this will be my last one.
난 이게 마지막이었으면 해
A little announcement.
자, 주목해주세요
내 신랑들러리는 나와 가장
절친한 친구 건터로 결정했어
I've decided that my best man
is my best friend Gunther.
What's my last name?
내 성이 뭔 줄 알아?
Central Perk?
센트럴퍼크?
Thanks for not marrying Rachel.
레이첼을 놔줘서 고마워
Hey, Gunther!
Don't forget your shirt.
건터, 셔츠 가져가요
그게 뭐야?
What are those?
Little party favors.
Check it out.
파티 기념품이야, 봐
로스 겔러의 총각파티
1998년
와, 멋지다
신랑들러리
조이 트리비아니
다시 주목하세요
Just want everybody to know the
position of my best man is still open.
내 신랑들러리 자리는
아직 공석입니다
그리고... 신부 자리도 역시
So is the position of the bride.
잘됐네요
Great.
Smooth, man.
진정해라
목에 칠리 붙었어
You got some chili on your neck.
I just want to say thanks, everyone.
This was great!
모두들 감사합니다
정말 즐거웠어요
월요일 아침에 보자고
See you guys Monday morning.
-Thanks, Joey.
-Don't forget your shirt.
- 수고했다, 조이
- 셔츠 챙겨야지
고마워
자, 박물관 괴짜 아저씨들
Hey, museum geeks!
Party's over.
파티는 끝났습니다
숙녀 분께 인사들 하시고
Wave bye-bye to the nice lady.
There you go.
각자 부모님네 지하실로 복귀
Back to your parents' basement.
All right.
Boys, come on out.
Here you go.
자, 이제 나오너라
어머, 귀여워라
당신 거예요?
Look at the birdies!
Are those yours?
네
They let you keep
chickens and ducks as pets?
닭이랑 오리를
애완용으로 키우시네?
그럼요, 오리는 훈련도
시켰답니다, 보세요
And I got the duck
totally trained too.
Stare at the wall.
벽을 봐
Hardly move.
동작 그만
하얗게 변해라
Be white.
You are good at that.
재주 참 좋으시네
I had fun tonight.
오늘 즐거웠어요
파티도 끝내줬구요
-You throw one hell of a party.
-Thanks. It was great meeting you.
고마워요
반가웠어요
만약 내 친구들이
결혼하거나 생일을 맞거나...
If any of my friends ever get married
or have a birthday or a Tuesday....
- 화요일이면...
- 네, 좋아요
Yeah, that'd be great.
그럼 잘 자요
So, I guess, good night.
Unless you want to hang around.
좀더 놀다 가지 그래요
- 그럴까요?
- 네
I'll let you play with my duck.
오리랑 놀게 해줄게요
이봐요
Stripper!
스트리퍼
반지 도둑이다!
The stripper stole the ring!
반지 도둑이다! 빨랑 일어나
스트리퍼가 반지를 훔쳐갔어
Chandler, get up!
The stripper stole the ring!
-What?
-The ring is gone!
- 뭐?
- 반지가 없어졌어
잠깐, 정신 좀 차리고
Just give me a minute
to wake up for this.
아하하!
You lost the ring.
You're the worst best man!
반지를 잃어버렸어?
넌 최악의 신랑들러리야
This isn't funny.
I go to sleep, everything's cool.
웃을 일이 아냐, 어떡하지?
잠들기 전엔 다 좋았는데
I wake up, the stripper's gone,
and the ring is gone!
아침에 일어나 보니
스트리퍼도 없고 반지도 없어
- 스트리퍼랑 잤어?
- 당연하지
-You slept with her?
-Of course!
-Hi, guys.
-Hi, Phoebe.
안녕, 얘들아
- 어서 와, 피비
- 왔니?
I wanted to apologize if I seemed
a tad edgy yesterday at my shower.
어제 파티에서 내가 좀
예민했었다면 사과할게
호르몬 때문이야
Just the hormones.
- 그걸 왜 모르겠니
- 호르몬 맞아
-No, we
-Hormones.
I wanted to say thank you.
It was so sweet.
마음 써줘서 얼마나
고마운지 모르겠다
오, 그래
많이 좋아져서 다행이다
You seem to be doing much better.
-How are things going?
-Good.
별일 없지?
좋아, 요즘은 너무 내 얘기만
하는 것 같다, 너희는 어때?
Everything's been about me lately.
So what's happening with you?
We were just talking about me
not going to Ross' wedding.
난 로스의 결혼식에
가지 않을 생각이야
It just might be too hard,
given the history and all that.
너무 힘들 것 같아
우린 사연이 너무 많잖니
그 얘기 들으니까
나 가출했을 때
This reminds me of the time
when I lived on the street.
자기랑 같이 자면 먹을 걸
사주겠다던 남자가 생각난다
This guy offered to buy me food
if I slept with him.
How is this like that?
그게 어떻게 비슷해?
그러고 보니 좀 다르구나
Well, let's see.
It's not really like that.
그건 현실적인 문제였고
Because that was an actual problem.
And yours is just a bunch
of high-school crap...
네 경우는 개뿔도 쓰잘데없는
고등학교 때 헛소리 아니겠니
...that nobody really gives!
I'm sorry. I just thought
- 미안해, 난 그냥...
- 또 수도꼭지 틀었다
Here come the water works.
I called the company that sent her,
and they don't care.
어떡하지? 스트리퍼 회사에
전화했더니 자기들은 모른대
911에선 나한테 소리만 질러
이게 긴급상황이 아니면 뭐냐
I called 911 and they yelled at me.
This is an emergency!
I really wanna help you out,
but I got plans to go see Titanic...
미안하지만 난 타이타닉 봐야 돼
언제 시작하는지 911에 물어볼래
...so I've got to call 911
to find out what time it starts.
Hey, guys.
얘들아
어서 와
Thanks again for last night.
What a great party.
어제는 정말 대단한 파티였어
동료들도 너무 좋아하는 거야
The guys from work had a blast.
한 명은 총각파티가
처음이었고
One of them had never been
to a bachelor party before.
그리고 또 한 명은
파티 자체가 처음이래
Another one had never been
to a party before.
So that wedding ring.
그 결혼반지 말이야
-Man, that is nice.
-Yeah, right?
진짜 멋지더라
그렇지?
나도 그런 걸 하나 사고 싶은데
어디 가면 구할 수 있을까
I might pick one of those
babies up for myself.
Where might one get one of those?
When my grandmother first came
to this country...
그 반지?
우리 할머니가 미국에 오실 때
그 반지랑 옷이 전 재산이었대
...that ring and the clothes on her back
were all she had with her.
그렇다면 이 세상에
둘도 없는 반지겠네?
So you might say
that the ring is irreplaceable.
Absolutely. It's been in my family
for generations.
당연하지
대대로 물려받은 거야
그 반지를 낀 신부는
오래오래 행복하게 산대
Every bride who's worn it
has lived a long and happy life.
So you might say it's a magic ring.
그럼 요술반지구나
Yeah, the stripper stole it.
그거 스트리퍼가 훔쳐갔다
어?
What?
왜?
방금 뭐라고...
-What did you just
-I think I heard what he said.
내가 들은 바에 의하면 이거야
I believe it was,
"The stripper stole the ring."
스트리퍼가 반지를 훔쳐갔다
내 반지를? 내 결혼반지를
스트리퍼가 훔쳐갔다는 거야?
My ring? My wedding ring?
The stripper stole my wedding ring?
어떻게 이런 일이 있지?
How could this happen?
이 말이 문제의 발단이었어
'조이, 네가 신랑들러리해라'
It all started when you said,
"Joey, you be my best man!"
All right.
I'm going to call the cops.
좋아, 경찰에 신고할게
I screwed up.
But you don't have to turn me in.
아무리 그렇다고
날 경찰에 넘길래?
-Not on you, on the stripper.
-I already did that.
너 말고 스트리퍼
신고는 내가 벌써 했어
살인범들 다 잡고 찾아본대
They said they'd look into it
after they solve all the murders.
-We'll call the company that sent her.
-I did that too.
그럼 그 여자 보낸
회사에 전화하자
그것도 했는데 본명이나
연락처는 알려줄 수 없대
They wouldn't give me her real name.
They said if I bother them again,
they'd call the police.
또 귀찮게 하면 신고한다더라
그때 반지 얘기도 하라고 했어
I said, "You talk to the police,
you tell them I'm missing a ring."
So, what are you telling me?
그래서 요지가 뭐야
손놓고 앉아있자고?
There's nothing we can do?
어떻게 이런 일이 있어
-How could this happen?
-Look, Ross, I am so sorry.
로스, 정말 죽을 죄를 졌다
전화해서 가짜 이름을 대고
내 사무실로 오라면 어떨까
What if we just called her...
...used a fake name
and had her come to my office?
That sounds like fun,
but we got a ring to find!
그것도 재미있겠지만
반지부터 찾아야지!
Here's your tea, Phoebe.
차 마셔라, 피비
It's so good.
정말 좋다
Thanks.
- 고마워
- 그래, 됐다
-Good.
-So glad you like it.
맘에 든다니 다행이다
What? She made the tea.
왜?
모니카가 끓였어
I think I just had a contraction.
아냐, 진통이 오나 봐
뭐라고?
-What?
-My God!
- 어떡해
- 맙소사
I felt one a few minutes ago.
몇 분 전부터 이상했는데
지금은 확실한 것 같아
That definitely was one.
You can't have the baby here.
여기서 낳으면 안돼, 남자애들
나간 뒤로 소독도 안 했다고
I haven't sterilized the apartment
since the guys moved out!
괜찮을 거야, 걱정 마, 안심해
물 끓이고 시트 몇 장 찢을게
It's okay. I'll boil some water
and rip up some sheets.
아냐, 출산이 가까워오면
가짜진통이 올 수도 있대
It's probably false labor.
That can happen near the end.
Just get the book.
누가 책이나 갖다 줘
-Get the book!
-The book!
- 레이첼, 책 가져와
- 그래
알았어
여기
-The Bible?
-I don't know!
- 성경?
- 나도 몰라!
All right. This is great.
그래, 시작하자
You get behind the desk.
챈들러, 넌 여기 앉아있어
그 여자는 널 몰라볼 거야
When she comes in,
she won't recognize you because
알 리가 없지?
Well, why would she?
And then you buzz Ross and l.
들어오면 우릴 불러
넌 미스터 곤잘레스
난 미스터 왕이야
You be Mr. Gonzales,
and I'll be Mr. Wong.
Diverse.
인종도 다양하군
Anybody call for security?
누가 경비를 부르셨나요?
You be cool.
다들 침착하게
좋아요, 어느 분이
건터 센트럴퍼크죠?
Which one is Gunther Central Perk?
Joey.
이런, 조이
내 반지 어디 있어, 돌아가신
할머니의 결혼반지 어쨌냐고!
Where's my ring?
My dead grandmother's wedding ring.
그게 침착이냐?
Way to be cool, man.
What?
무슨 말이에요?
There was a ring in a box.
After you left, it was gone.
침대 옆 탁자에 반지를 뒀는데
당신이 나간 다음에 사라졌어
You think I stole some ring?
- 내가 훔쳤다는 거예요?
- 그렇습니다!
당신 짓인 거 다 아니까
시간 끌지 말고 자백하쇼
We know you took it!
Just save yourself the time and confess.
Who are you, the Hardy Boys?
댁들이 무슨 탐정이야?
일주일에 1,600을 버는 내가
뭐가 아쉬워서 그딴 걸 훔치나
I don't need to steal a stupid ring.
I make $1,600 a week.
Any of you guys make that?
그렇게 버는 사람 있어요?
Marry me.
결혼합시다
I don't get it. It was in my room all night.
She didn't take it.
귀신이 곡할 노릇이군
밤새 내 방에 있었어
그 여자도 아니고 나도 아니고
너도 아니면 누구 짓이냐고
I didn't take it.
You didn't take it. Then who did?
쉿! 생각 좀 하자
We're trying to think.
I don't get how you know
it's false labor.
어떻게 가짜진통을
구별할 수 있어?
Do you see any babies?
아기 나왔니?
-How do you feel?
-Okay, I guess.
기분은 어때?
괜찮은 것 같아
I don't know.
모르겠어
I know it's going
to be over soon so....
곧 끝나겠지 뭐
But isn't that a good thing?
하지만 잘된 일이잖아
-You said you were sick of this.
-I know.
많이 힘들다면서
나도 알아
Usually, when you're done
with the pregnant thing...
보통 출산 후에는
엄마노릇을 하잖아
...you get to do the mom thing.
But I'll be sitting around in my
leather pants, drinking tequila.
근데 난 가죽바지 입고
테킬라나 마시고 있겠다
Some moms do that.
그런 엄마도 있어
That's even sadder.
그게 더 슬프다
Look, I know what I got myself into.
물론 내가 자초한 일이지
It's just that
now that they're in me...
내 뱃속에 든 아기들...
...it's like I know them and....
정이 너무 많이 들었어
얘들을 보내는 게
쉽지는 않을 거야
It just won't be easy
when these babies have to go away.
I know, sweetie.
그건 이해하지만
좋은 쪽으로 생각해봐
But it's not like
you won't have anything.
조카들이 생기잖아
그게 더 나을 수도 있어
You'll have nieces and nephews.
That's even better.
-Yeah, okay.
-No, really.
그래, 알았다
아니, 정말이야
You won't be the one
worrying about saving for college.
애들 대학등록금
걱정 안 해도 되고
말썽부린다고
야단칠 필요도 없고
Or yelling at them when they're bad.
Or putting them on Ritalin
when they just won't calm down.
떠들 때 진정제를
먹일 필요도 없어
안 그래?
가출이나 성문제로 고민할 때
널 찾아와 상담할 거야
You'll be the one they run away to.
The one they talk to about sex.
멋진 피비 고모가 되겠지
You just get to be cool Aunt Phoebe.
Cool Aunt Phoebe.
멋진 피비 고모?
I am pretty cool.
내가 멋지긴 하지
And you know what else?
Are they going to love you!
또 걔들이 널 얼마나
사랑할지 생각해봐
They are going to love me.
좀 그렇겠지?
Thanks, you guys. Again.
고맙다
- 너희들밖에 없어
- 우리 피비...
Oh, sweetie.
Thanks.
고마워, 오!
What?
- 왜, 맙소사
- 아파?
Just kidding.
장난이야
Oh, my God!
- 왜
- 어떡해
너희들 진짜 잘 속는다
Got you again.
You're so easy!
If anything happens to him
- 무슨 일이 생기면...
- 조이, 간단한 수술이랬어
The vet said
it's a simple procedure.
잘못될 가능성은
얼마든지 있어
Things can go wrong.
What if he doesn't make it?
- 실패하면 어쩌지?
- 잘될 거야
-He will, Joe.
-But what if he doesn't?
잘못되면 어떡하냐고
He's such a good duck.
진짜 좋은 오리인데
I'm so worried about him!
정말 걱정스럽다
Somebody lose a ring?
어느 분 반지죠?
Oh, my God!
Thank you! Thank you so much!
세상에! 정말 감사합니다!
How's the duck?
우리 오리는 어떤가요?
안정을 취하는 중이니
곧 볼 수 있을 겁니다
Just fine.
You'll see him in a bit.
잘됐다
Great.
맘고생 시켜서
정말 미안하다
-Thanks for being so cool.
-No, that's all right.
- 아냐, 괜찮아
- 괜찮긴 뭐가
You made me your best man
and I totally let you down.
날 들러리로 선택했는데
실망만 안겨줬잖아
-It's not your fault.
-Yeah, it is.
- 이건 네 잘못이 아냐
- 내 잘못이야
You wouldn't have lost it.
너라면 반지를
안 잃어버렸을 거야
Ross, you were right.
He should be your best man.
이거 알아?
네 처음 생각이 맞았어
얘가 들러리를 서야 돼
-No, you should.
-Don't argue.
아냐, 네가 해
- 글쎄 잔소리 말고...
- 야야, 난 결정했어
I get to choose my best man.
I want both you guys.
너희 둘이 맡아줘
Really?
- 진짜?
- 정말?
Both you guys should be
up there with me.
둘 다 내 옆에 있어야지
You two are my
너희 같은 친구를 둬서...
난 얼마나 행복한 사람인지...
I'm lucky to have just one good
고맙다 야
Thanks, man.
I got to go check something, okay?
저쪽엔 뭐가 있나?
-What a baby!
-Total wuss.
- 못난 자식
- 계집애라니까
-How come you're getting Nana's ring?
-Mom gave it to me.
할머니 반지는
어떻게 찾았어?
엄마가 주시더라, 너한테는
필요 없을 거라고 하시면서
She said something about it being
a wedding ring and that you may not need...
...one.
왜?
I really didn't need to tell you all that.
괜히 말했는갑다
I don't really think it's fair.
I mean, I've always loved that ring.
이건 불공평해
내가 점찍어둔 건데
Oh, Mon, I'm sorry.
미안하다
I'd let you have it,
but Emily's gotten really attached to it.
너한테 주고 싶지만
에밀리가 너무 좋아해
할 수 없지 뭐
Thanks.
고마워요
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
여기요
- 고마워요
- 에밀리
Emily, did you know that that ring spent
two days in a duck's colon?
그 반지 이틀이나 오리 내장에
들어가 있었던 거 알아요?